musicclout.com 2015-04-19

# Music Clout

### Privacy Policy

**The effective date of this Privacy Policy is February 2011**

MusicClout.com has created this privacy policy to show our commitment in protecting your personal information and informing you about how we handle it. This will help you understand how we collect, use and safeguard your personal information that you provide to us on our website. Music Clout's policy is to respect the privacy of its members. Music Clout will not monitor, edit, or disclose any personal information about you or your account, including its contents, without your prior permission unless Music Clout believes that such action is necessary or if it is required to do so to. 

Please review this privacy policy periodically as we may modify it from time to time. Each time you visit the MusicClout.com or provide us with information, by doing so you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy at that time.

**Information We Collect From You**  
In order to operate the Site and to provide you with information about products or services that may be of interest to you, we may collect and store your personal that would be used to contact you directly such as your contact name, email address, and phone number. We use your email address and your other personal information to help us efficiently operate the Site, to contact you in connection with your transactions and other activities on the site such as your inquiries, suggestions about our website, and communicating with you about our service in general. 

**Information Other Websites Collect From You**  
On the Site, we place links to other Websites operated by other parties. Some of these other Websites contain our brand names and trademarks and other intellectual property that we own; others do not. When you click on these links and visit these other Websites, regardless of whether or not they contain our brand names, trademarks and other intellectual property, you need to be aware that we do not control these other Websites or these other Websites' business practices, and that this privacy policy does not apply to these other Websites. Consequently, the operators of these other Websites may collect different kinds of information about you, and may use and disclose that information in different ways than we would if it were collected on the Site. We encourage you to review their privacy policies and remind you that we will not be responsible for their actions.

**Cookies**  
Our website, like many websites, uses cookies to keep track of your purchases and other activity on our website and enhance your experience on our website. We also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your password, and if you choose, to save other personal information so you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit our website. If you wish to disable these cookies, the "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how. However, if you set your browser to disable cookies, you may not be able to access certain areas on our website.

**Your IP Address**  
Like most e-commerce websites, each time you visit our website, we collect your IP address and the web page from which you came. In order to administer and optimize our website for you and to diagnose problems with our website, we use your IP address to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information about you.

**How We Use Financial Information**  
We use your financial information to check your qualifications, to bill you for products and services and to enable you to participate in discount, rebate and similar programs in which you may elect to participate. By making a purchase, or engaging in any other kind of activity or transaction that uses financial information, on our website, you consent to our providing your financial information to our service providers and to such third parties as we determine are necessary to support and process your activities and transactions, as well as to your credit card issuer for their purposes. These third parties may include the credit card companies and banking institutions used to process and support the transaction or activity. 

**How We Protect the Security of Your Information**  
MusicClout.com has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Our secure server software (SSL) is the industry standard and among the best software available today for secure commerce transactions. We encrypt all of your personal and financial information as it travels over the Internet and we store your financial information on our servers in encrypted form. Your information may be transferred to and maintained on computer networks which may be located outside of the state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction in which you reside, and the country or jurisdiction in which these computer networks are located may not have privacy laws as protective as the laws in your country or jurisdiction.

**Changing our Privacy Policy for Previously Gathered Information**  
If at any point Music Clout decides to make any changes to the Privacy Policy we will automatically update this information with an effected date on our homepage. Please note that we will continue to have the right to change our privacy policy and practices, and how we use your personally identifiable information, without notice, as described in the first paragraph of this Privacy Policy, provided that such changes shall only apply to information gathered on or after the date of the change.

If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy you can contact us. 

© 2011 Music Clout. All rights reserved.
